<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PinkTalk</title><link>https://pinktalk.doowonee.com/en/</link><description>Recent content on PinkTalk</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ko</language><atom:link href="https://pinktalk.doowonee.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Terms of service</title><link>https://pinktalk.doowonee.com/en/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pinktalk.doowonee.com/en/terms-of-service/</guid><description>Article 1. Purpose PinkTalk is a service provided by Doowonee (&amp;ldquo;Company”) via mobile apps(ios, android, etc.). This Terms of service prescribes general provisions about the rights, duties and responsibilities, terms of use, and procedures required in use of the Service. The Company appreciates your taking time to read it carefully.
Article 2. Definition of Terms &amp;ldquo;User&amp;rdquo; refers to all of people who use PinkTalk even disagree to This Terms of Service.</description></item><item><title>Privacy policy</title><link>https://pinktalk.doowonee.com/en/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pinktalk.doowonee.com/en/privacy-policy/</guid><description>1. What Privacy Policy Means for Our Users PinkTalk uses and provides the user’s personal information based on the user’s consent, and actively guarantees the user’s right(the right to control one’s own personal information). PinkTalk complies with applicable laws, personal information protection regulations and guidelines of the Republic of Korea, which must be obeyed by information communication service providers. PinkTalk&amp;rsquo;s Privacy Policy refers to guidelines on protecting the user’s valuable personal information which PinkTalk is required to comply with, in order to ensure that users use its services with confidence.</description></item></channel></rss>